<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Services on Marketise Me - online marketing and website development.</title>
    <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Services on Marketise Me - online marketing and website development.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Design</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/mail-campaigns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/mail-campaigns/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Consultations</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/marketing-consult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/marketing-consult/</guid>
      <description>The marketing strategy for positioning the product / service aims to create a unique product proposal that will dominate the target group&amp;rsquo;s mind. We create SWOT analysis and identify the strengths and favors of your brand as well as the potential for future development and the dangers of your competitors in the market environment.
Together, we build a plan and a strategy that relates to your business goals. We monitor the implementation of each item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/ad-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/ad-campaign/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/sem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/sem/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays every business has a website and almost any of them uses Google Ads.
Sites that go back to the rankings can remain &amp;ldquo;invisible&amp;rdquo; as nearly 80% of all users are browsing only the first results page. To be in the forefront, your brand needs an effective optimization in search engine machine - SEO (Search Engine Optimization) and PPC (Pay Per Click) advertising.
Reach new customers on the Internet in an extremely efficient and cost-effective way and regain the money you invested (ROI - Return of Investment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing – Facebook &amp; Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/social/</guid>
      <description>By absorbing the strength of marketing foundations in social networks, Marketise Me&amp;rsquo;s team will help you increase your online presence, your audience, the users of your products or services multiple times.
We offer professional services related to social network marketing, Facebook page support, Instagram account, and Google Ads ad.
We give you the opportunity to keep in touch with your customers online by creating and publishing interesting, varied and targeted content on your page or profile that is fully tailored to and consistent with your business, brand or project according to your personal preferences and requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Experience</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/ux/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Development</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/webdesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/webdesign/</guid>
      <description>We will create a unique and responsive design tailored to your vision and functionality requirements. Design suitable for any device - computers, laptops, mobile devices, tablets.
Our creative programmers, marketers, search engine optimizers (SEO) and web designers do not just create websites, they create a virtual art that will highlight your business from others.
In the process of work, we strive to create an attractive site, which is at the forefront of search engine results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Process</title>
      <link>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/working-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:53:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marketiseme.com/en/service/working-process/</guid>
      <description>At the end of this phase, we will have the basics of your digital marketing strategy that will guide the rest of the process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>